<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Janssen Decision Modeling in R Workshop</title>
    <link>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Janssen Decision Modeling in R Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/home/hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/home/hero/</guid>
      <description>This is the website for a 4-day hands-on workshop: Janssen Decision Modeling in R Workshop.
The Decision Analysis in R for Technologies in Health (DARTH) workgroup is offering a workshop on decision modeling in R exclusively for Janssen. The workshop will be offered virtually via Zoom. Co-instructors Eva Enns, Petros Pechlivanoglou, Hawre Jalal, Fernando Alarid-Escudero, Eline Krijkamp and Alan Yang will cover the principles of decision-analytic modeling and will guide participants in developing fundamental skills in R, building cohort state-transition models in R, and conducting probabilistic sensitivity analysis in R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About this workshop</title>
      <link>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/home/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/home/intro/</guid>
      <description>Health and public health resources are limited and policymakers are under increased pressure to make use of these resources as efficiently as possible. Decision analysis is a quantitative decision-making framework used to formalize objectives, quantify tradeoffs, and ultimately support more informed decision making. These techniques have been applied to a wide range of health policy questions, including optimal cancer screening and treatment guidelines; technology reimbursement and coverage decisions; and hospital operations management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop objectives</title>
      <link>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/home/objectives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/home/objectives/</guid>
      <description>Overall learning objectives for the course include;
 Overview of decision-analytic modeling in R Explain research scenarios that require decision-analytic modeling methods Develop and manage data for decision-analytic modeling Analyze and interpret Markov models Perform probabilistic sensitivity analysis Develop competence in R for performing decision analytic techniques  We will cover the following topics:
April 6 - 15: Intro to R for Decision Modeling (part 1)
Friday, April 16: Intro to R for Decision Modeling (part 2)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>