<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome on Janssen Decision Modeling in R Workshop</title>
    <link>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome on Janssen Decision Modeling in R Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Opportunities to learn</title>
      <link>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/opportunities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/opportunities/</guid>
      <description>Workshops and courses Decision Analysis in R for Technologies in Health (DARTH)
DARTH workshops
The Society for Medical Decision Making (SMDM)
SMDM short courses
ISPOR - The Professional Society for Health Economics and Outcomes Research
ISPOR short courses
Degree programs University of Minnesota
HEALTH SERVICES RESEARCH, POLICY &amp;amp; ADMINISTRATION PHD
HEALTH SERVICES RESEARCH, POLICY &amp;amp; ADMINISTRATION (MS)
University of Toronto
MSc in Health Services Research - Health Technology Assessment stream</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install software</title>
      <link>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/system/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/system/</guid>
      <description>In this workshop, we will use R and RStudio. Please install R and RStudio on your machine prior to the start of the workshop.
 If you will be using a CDC-issued computer to participate in the workshop, please work with your IT office to install R v4.0.2 and Rstudio on your computers as soon as possible.
 If you will be using a personal machine, please follow the installation instructions below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparation</title>
      <link>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/local/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/local/</guid>
      <description>Virtual attendance  The workshop will be offered virtually via Zoom (online/teaching platform)
 We will use Slack as our primary communication platform
  What do I need to do before the workshop? You&amp;rsquo;ll need to complete the following items:
Set up Slack
This is our main platform for communications for participants and instructors for this workshop. Everyone should complete this step.
Install software
We will use R and RStudio for this workshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instructors</title>
      <link>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/instructors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/instructors/</guid>
      <description>Eva Enns, PhD  
   Eva Enns, PhD, is an Associate Professor at the University of Minnesota’s School of Public Health, in the division of Health Policy and Management. She has a bachelor’s degree in electrical engineering from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, and holds both a Master’s and a PhD in electrical engineering from Stanford University. She develops mathematical models of the spread of infectious diseases that help evaluate strategies aimed at mitigating disease impact through prevention and/or treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A virtual workshop</title>
      <link>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/accommodations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/accommodations/</guid>
      <description> The workshop will be offered virtually via Zoom. If you have not used Zoom before, please follow setup instructions here.
List of things you will need  Your computer A working microphone Stable Internet connection A webcam (optional, we&amp;rsquo;d like to meet you!)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/tutorials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/tutorials/</guid>
      <description>Decision modeling tutorials: We have published a number of modeling tutorials and methodology papers. A list of them can be found here.
DARTH GitHUB This is our group&amp;rsquo;s GitHub page where we host different repositories for different projects, tutorials and packages like dampack, darthpack, and darthtools.
R tutorials: R-handbook by DARTH
This comprehensive handbook for using R covers a wide range of topics in detail and is publically available on DARTH&amp;rsquo;s GitHub repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set up Slack</title>
      <link>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/slack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/slack/</guid>
      <description>We will use Slack as the main platform for online communications. Throughout and after the workshop, we encourage the instructors and the participants to stay connected on Slack to exchange ideas, discuss problems and seek help from each other.
Click here to join the Slack workspace for this workshop. Please email alan.yang@sickkids.ca if you are unable to join. After you join, you can access the workspace via its URL.
We encourage you to give us a short introduction about yourself in the main chat room once you join!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time and location</title>
      <link>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/time-and-location/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://decision-modeling-for-public-health-ajgh02sd.netlify.app/prework/time-and-location/</guid>
      <description>When Friday, April 16
Tuesday, April 20
Friday, April 23
Thurs, April 29
8AM - 12PM Eastern Time
Where Virtual meeting on Zoom</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>